[theme music playing]
HIERARCHY
[music fades]
[tender music playing]
[Woo-jin] Mmm.
[Woo-jin moans]
Good morning. You sleep all right?
[chuckles] Mm-mm.
[Woo-jin moans]
Time to wake up.
[Woo-jin] Mm-mm.
[kisses]
Did you sleep all right?
[woman] Mmm.
[distant train horn blares]
Don't be late, okay?
[Woo-jin chuckles]
-[Woo-jin] I'll see you at school.
-See ya!
[pensive music playing]
EPISODE 2
SECRET: WITHIN A SECRET
[pensive music continues]
-We're finished.
-[engines roaring]
I'm done. [echoes]
[pensive music continues]
[exhales forcefully]
[stirring music playing]
[operatic music playing]
[music continues muffled]
[music continues as normal]
[music fades]
I trust you've all been well.
Hand out their gifts.
We're very grateful, ma'am.
[Ri-an] I didn't think
I'd see you until next month.
Ri-an, my dear son.
You're looking well.
My business in Singapore ended early,
so I thought I'd visit.
How's school? A third-year already!
My, how time flies.
You'll be in college before we know it.
A mother gets emotional.
They grow up so fast.
I'm a second-year.
Hmm?
I still have a year before I graduate.
That's wonderful! Have you thought about
what university you'd like to attend?
Perhaps… England would be a good fit?
Oh.
Let's get my schedule in order.
Yes, ma'am.
[pensive music playing]
Lunch with the executives at 12:00.
Jooshin Gallery at 2:00.
Jooshin Hotel at 4:00.
And… what else was there?
[man] You have a meeting with Director An.
-I'll squeeze the director in after lunch.
-[man] Right.
[mother] Everything in London
is marvelous, except the weather.
Choose somewhere in the UK.
You won't regret it.
[Ri-an] You've been gone three months.
We haven't had a real conversation
in over a year.
You could at least ask me how I'm doing.
Like, if I'm eating all right,
or if I've been sick!
I'm not a grown-up.
I still need my parents sometimes.
How many staff members
have I assigned to take care of Ri-an?
Six tutors, two assistants,
three health specialists,
and four nutritionists.
Fifteen total, ma'am.
What kind of attention are you lacking?
[breathes deeply]
And let's set something up with CEO Ryu
before the board meeting.
[man] Yes, ma'am.
[engine revving]
[sighs]
[indistinct chattering]
Oh! Tae-ho!
Hey!
[indistinct chattering]
[scoffs] Jesus Christ.
Get your dirty hands off me,
you charity case!
[student 1] Hey, Tae-ho.
[pensive music playing]
[student 2 chuckles] Man,
you really don't have a clue, do you?
-Do you know Tae-ho?
-[student 3] Of course he doesn't.
Does he look like he's friends
with the heir to Jaeyul Hotels?
Look, scholarship kid,
going here doesn't make you our friend.
-[Ha laughs]
-[student 3] He laughed!
-Wow!
-[student 2] In our faces!
This commoner thinks he can just come up
and touch the nobles whenever he wants.
[student 2] Tae-ho should wash
his shoulder. It might start rotting off.
-[camera shutter clicking]
-Ooh, look.
Ooh!
[Ye-ji] No way!
He actually showed his face?
Ri-an's gonna make
an unboxing video with his guts.
He's got nerve, that's for sure.
Seriously, what was going on that night?
How could Jae-i just stand there
and let that scholarship kid kiss her?
Maybe she was into it.
[Ye-ji] Ugh, no way!
Jae-i with a scholarship kid?
She would never! Would she, He-ra?
I wouldn't rule it out.
Scholarship or not,
if Jae-i likes him, that's that.
Actually, it's inspiring.
To be attracted to someone without regard
to their status or social class.
[Ye-ji] Really?
So what about you, He-ra?
Does that rule apply to you?
Oh, I'm different.
I could never be attracted to a man
that much poorer than I am.
It's just in my DNA.
Oh. Hey, he's coming.
[indistinct chattering]
[female student] You don't wanna get
on their bad side.
Everything Chan-min said
the other day is true.
The kid who died,
it was because he pissed off Ri-an.
They said it was a hit-and-run,
but that's bullshit.
He was so scared of Ri-an's goons,
he ran into traffic.
[intriguing music playing]
Or somebody hit him on purpose.
[Ha] But why?
What did he do to piss off Ri-an?
[female student] It was because of Jae-i.
He was friends with Jae-i,
and Ri-an didn't like it.
-What? You mean, that's all?
-"That's all"? Jae-i's his girlfriend!
His Achilles heel.
She's the only thing he cares about!
[rhythmic pop music playing]
[Ri-an] Tell me something.
Was that little show really necessary?
What do you mean, "show"?
The kiss?
What I said earlier
should have been enough.
I've been perfectly clear to you.
Who I like
and what I choose to do with them
has nothing to do with you.
You like that guy?
The scholarship kid?
What's really going on here?
What's the real reason
you're calling it off all of a sudden?
And why are you
bringing the new kid into it?
You said you'd die
before you told me the truth,
but I need to know, Jung Jae-i.
Matter of fact,
I'm not letting you get away
without an explanation.
I can promise you right now
I'm willing to do whatever it takes.
Whatever it takes to find out
the secret you're keeping from me.
And I won't stop
until you're back were you belong.
[rhythmic pop music continues]
I'll take care of that prick. Quietly.
No, not quietly.
I want everybody to know.
He needs to learn
that there are consequences
for putting his hands on what's mine.
Don't you think
we should lay low for a little while
when that other kid just died?
[music fades]
Okay, I'll take care of it.
He'll get the message.
[Yun-seok] From this moment on,
any asshole that speaks
to the new scholarship student,
or even acknowledges him,
will get the same treatment.
Chan-min.
[Chan-min groaning in pain]
I shouldn't have to tell you
how to handle this stuff.
I mean, do I have to
hold your fucking hand through everything?
[Chan-min] You're right.
It won't happen again.
I was actually
just in the middle of a plan.
A plan to take care of him!
[Ha laughing]
[laughing continues]
I'm sorry.
I've never seen anyone make these plans
in front of their target.
[scoffs]
-Have you?
-Do you have a death wish, motherfucker?
[pensive music playing]
Hey, Yun-seok just told you
not to speak to me.
Or did you not hear him?
You crazy fucker…
[Chan-min groaning]
[camera shutter clicks]
-[Ha] Chan-min!
-Hey!
If you should be hitting someone now,
it should be him instead of me, right?
Hmm?
[in pain] Ah! My fingers!
Shit! You son of a bitch!
Why are you all fucking standing there?
[Chan-min grunts in pain]
Ugh, this is fucking bullshit!
[Chan-min grunts, groans]
Asshole!
[woman] What do you think you're doing?
A third-year?
What are you doing down here?
[Chan-min] Shit! So fucking embarrassing!
[breathes deeply]
[woman] I have
a brief announcement to make.
This year's Healing Forest retreat
will go ahead as planned.
All the details
will be posted in the group chat.
If you're unable to attend,
please notify me in advance.
That's all.
[sighs]
Jae-i.
Hang on. Can we talk for a minute?
Yeah.
Just say it.
Don't worry about her.
[clears throat]
You heard her.
I'm sorry… about the other night.
-I'm sorry if what I did offended you--
-Scholarship kid.
Kang Ha. That's my name.
Not "scholarship kid." Kang Ha.
Whatever your name is,
we were just fooling around at a party.
That's it. I hate it when guys get clingy.
Oh, do you want some advice?
I'm paying you back
for the shirt you lent me the other day.
Drop out.
"Drop out"?
Why should I drop out now?
Ri-an hates you, so that's the only thing
you can do to defend yourself.
[Ha] Ah.
If it's about that,
I can take care of myself.
And also…
[chuckles] …I liked kissing you.
I liked that it was you.
And I really liked that you didn't
push me away.
[chuckles]
[Jae-i scoffs]
[chuckles softly]
[He-ra] I'm rooting for you,
this passionate romance
between the classes.
But what made you choose Jae-i?
There were plenty of girls there.
She was pretty.
What?
She was the prettiest.
That night.
Out of every girl there.
[chuckles softly]
[acoustic guitar music playing]
That's it?
You put your life on the line
all because she was… cute?
[scoffs]
[acoustic guitar music continues]
[Ri-an] I mean,
I thought I had to do something.
I'm sorry.
Whatever I did,
I'm sorry for everything.
[poignant pop music playing]
[Jae-i laughs on video]
[Jae-i] How do I look? Pretty cool, huh?
[Ri-an] It suits you.
Hop in. I'll give you a ride somewhere.
-[Jae-i laughs]
-[Ri-an] Shall we?
[chuckles]
[Ri-an] Got you on camera.
-[Ri-an laughs]
-Ah!
[laughing]
[Jae-i laughs]
[Ri-an] What are you eating?
-[Jae-i] Ice cream.
-All to yourself? You're not gonna share?
Here. Here, have some.
-[Ri-an] Ah!
-Ah.
I'm gonna need you a little closer.
-[Jae-i] Give it to me. [laughs]
-Ah!
[Jae-i] Seriously! Hey!
Enough!
[both laughing]
-[Jae-i] Hey, hey.
-[Ri-an moans playfully]
-[Jae-i] Hey!
-[Ri-an screams playfully]
[Ri-an groaning]
Are you sorry?
Don't mess with people's food.
Ice cream or me?
Ice cream.
Huh? Get back here.
Now you're in for it.
Say "ah!"
Come on, open wide!
I can't reach that far.
-Ah!
-[Jei-i] Ah-- Hey!
That was your fault!
-[Ri-an] You're right. It's my fault.
-You admit it?
[Ri-an] I admit it.
-But one thing.
-What?
[door opens]
[Ri-an] Are you willing
to beat up your boyfriend over ice cream?
-[Jae-i] Well, you deserved it.
-Ice cream or me. Choose.
-[Jae-i] Well, it's obvious…
-[Ri-an] Oh yeah?
-[Jae-i] I choose…
-[Ri-an] Yes?
-[Jae-i] Ice cream.
-Not gonna cry, are you?
-[Ri-an] Come here.
-[Jae-i laughs]
-[Ri-an] Seriously, come here!
-Aren't you just a hopeless romantic?
You know, this is a bit of a turnoff.
[music fades]
I saw Jae-i outside the hotel.
[pensive music playing]
Are you even listening to me?
Stop moping. It's gross.
Cut it out.
Remember, Jae-i hates it
when guys get too clingy.
I know something you can try.
What are you thinking?
Try dating someone else.
Since you were 15-- No, even longer.
Ever since you guys were six,
you've never given any other girl
so much as a second glance.
Seeing you with someone else
would drive her crazy.
I know if it were me, I'd want you back.
So I should date someone else
to lure her back?
Yeah. Or pretend to. Just be convincing.
Poor girl.
I'm sure she still has feelings for you.
Why else would she drive out here?
You need to get smart about this soon
if you're serious about winning her back.
This is your only shot.
[inhales deeply]
Well then…
you should
look into something.
Look into what, exactly?
The reason that she's leaving.
The real reason.
I don't think I can.
No one wants you back together
more than I do, but I'm her best friend.
I can't start spying on her, can I?
[melodic pop music playing]
-[Woo-jin] Been a while.
-Good to see you.
[Woo-jin] Just tell me, already.
Tell you what?
We both know you have a secret.
Why suffer through it alone?
You can share.
[phone buzzing]
Let me take this.
Looks like I'm not
the only one with a secret.
What happened to sharing?
I'll be right back.
[phone buzzes]
[mysterious music playing]
[distorted male voice]
If you keep ignoring me,
I'll consider sending this
to your father too.
[echoes] …your father too.
This is the email address
for the secretary's office
at Jaeyul Group, right?
[Jae-i breathes nervously]
[sighs]
[computer beeping]
[In-han] You said you took care of it.
You deleted everything, right?
So what's the problem?
[grunts]
[item clatters]
[Jae-i breathing anxiously]
[Jae-i whimpers]
[In-han] You're positive?
You're sure you did?
Yes, I'm sure.
I checked twice.
No, three times. I'm absolutely sure.
What do I do now?
What's gonna happen to me?
What the hell do I do?
[Jae-i whimpers]
Don't worry, we'll find a way.
No, it's too late for that.
I did everything I could.
-[In-han] Jae-i.
-You have no idea.
You don't know what my dad is like.
When he finds out,
he'll hide me away like my mom.
Or he'll just kill me.
At this point,
it'd be better if I just…
if I just died before it gets out.
We'll figure something out.
I can help you.
[sobs] I'm so scared
I'll end up like my mom!
I'm scared that my dad will kill me!
[Jae-i sobs]
[sniffles]
Wait.
[tense music playing]
Don't tell me…
[student 1] Jae-i? What? Hey! Hey!
-What are you doing in here?
-Jae-i!
-[student 1] Get out before we beat you.
-Jae-i! Wait, please!
-Jae-i!
-[student 1] Get out!
[tense music continues]
[male distorted voice] How about it?
Are you interested in speaking to me now?
[melodic pop music playing]
[Woo-jin sighs]
[breathes deeply]
-You're leaving?
-Yeah.
I'm tired. See you later.
[gunshot echoes]
[Jae-hyeok exclaims]
You nearly had it! [laughs]
Close one, Dad.
-[phone buzzing]
-Chairman Jung.
[phone buzzing]
I said don't disturb me.
What?
[stirring music playing]
What was uploaded?
[chuckles]
Confirm the details and stand by for now.
[tense music playing]
Tell me it isn't true, Jung Jae-i.
No daughter of mine
could do something like that.
I'd expect this kind of thing
out of your filthy, low-class mother.
But you? There's no way.
I refuse to believe
my daughter would humiliate me like this.
[gun clicks]
Answer me.
-Don't stand there gaping like a fool!
-[gun cocks]
[dog barking]
-[laughing]
-Answer me right now!
I'm afraid I have to go.
-[tense music subsides]
-[Jae-i exhales]
An issue has come up at work.
Oh really? It must be bad news.
Something odd was posted
on the board members' forum.
I have to assess the situation.
I feel awful. We haven't been
hunting together for a while.
Now I've gone and ruined it.
Don't rush coming back down.
[sighs, clears throat]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
There we go. Now the lemon zest.
Director Jang called.
He's been trying to reach you all morning.
Everything's all right at work?
Of course it is. We're fine.
And have you heard back from Jooshin?
I told you not to worry.
Oh. Is it today already?
Only the most special day of the year!
The day that I get to prepare
my daughter's breakfast myself!
[chuckles]
[phone alert]
[Jae-i] Come see me at the house later.
Am I your servant now?
[student 1 laughs]
That shit is so funny, man.
[student 2] That's not the craziest part.
Later…
[student 3] Hey.
[student 2] Let's go.
[beeping]
[locker door closes]
-[unsettling music playing]
-[Ha sighs]
[In-ha] They spiked my drink
with something.
It had to be some kind of drug.
I almost died.
I'm serious.
Wait. In-han. Just try and calm down.
You think high school kids would do that?
You have no idea
what kind of place Jooshin is…
what kind of people they are.
[sighs in frustration]
[unsettling music continues]
[Ri-an] Were your parent's fired
from Jooshin or something?
Were they contractors
whose business dried up?
Who the hell are you?
What's your deal, huh?
Everyone keeps telling me you're the one
who runs things around here.
I'm only doing what I need to survive.
If I have to go up against you
to do that, so be it.
That true?
You sure?
You see, I wanna know
what you're up to, scholarship kid.
Try me.
We'll see how long you last.
[Ha] In-han was being bullied, assaulted,
and Kim Ri-an was behind it.
Could he have spiked In-han's drink too?
[sighs]
[indistinct chattering]
We need to deal with him
at the Healing Forest.
If we wait any longer, we're dead!
But, Chan-min, he didn't even flinch
when you tried to hit him.
How do we get
someone like that to drop out?
We just have to kill his spirit!
Either we kick his face in
or deal with him like Kang In-han,
make him disappear.
No one would bat an eye
if another lowlife died anyway.
Get off your fucking phone
when I'm talking to you!
Ugh! These fucking idiots!
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
[door opens]
[music fades]
[door closes]
Ms. Han asked me to bring you this.
[woman] Mm-hmm.
How's it going?
And how is everyone?
Who exactly do you mean by that?
Ri-an, Jae-i, Woo-jin, He-ra.
I'm talking about your friends.
My friends?
They're all fine.
[woman] Don't waste your time
with the wrong people.
The friends you make here
will last a lifetime.
They'll be very helpful
when you start your career.
You understand what I mean, don't you?
Yes.
One thing, Mom.
How did you cover it up?
[pensive music playing]
In-han's death, I mean.
You made sure
there wasn't even a single article.
I'm curious how.
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
Go on, you'll be late.
-[sighs]
-[door opens]
[door closes]
[Ha] You have to open it.
I saw Kim Ri-an put drugs
into Choi Yun-seok's locker.
[music fades]
[Ms. Han] It's against school policy
to open a student's personal locker.
It's a breach of privacy.
If you don't open it for me,
I'll file a formal complaint.
A formal complaint? For?
You saw me being attacked
in the classroom, and you just ignored it.
[Ms. Han sighs]
Kang Ha, a school is a tiny society.
At Jooshin, we give students the freedom
to resolve minor issues amongst themselves
to help them function within that society.
Help us? Help us how?
Help us learn respect for the bosses' sons
since they'll be our bosses in the future?
Help us remember we're poor,
and that we'd better get used to
getting walked all over?
That doesn't sound much like "help" to me.
Or does it to you?
Kang Ha!
Maybe I should let the press know
about my assault,
about Jooshin's special rules.
Everything.
[Ms. Han sighs]
[stirring music playing]
[tense music playing]
[keypad beeps]
[Ba-da] Boo!
Oh, you scared me.
I'm so hungry. Buy me a yogurt?
-Yogurt?
-Mm-hmm.
Come on.
-Strawberry?
-Sure.
Is this it?
Is this what you were talking about?
You see? We need an investigation.
Find out what these are.
Find out who is dealing them
to who at school, and also,
who they might have fed them to.
This is Xanax.
They're for anxiety disorders.
I don't know if these were prescribed
at your old school, but they are here.
Most kids are under so much pressure,
they need them.
Go check with a police station
or hospital if you don't believe me.
Just put it back before anyone finds out.
And don't cause any trouble.
[sighs in frustration]
[music fades]
[Jae-i] If someone's sending you
anonymous DMs,
can you find out who they are?
I'm not sure.
Why do you ask?
Well, you said you knew
a good harassment lawyer.
Oh, yes, I do.
Eun-gyeong used this firm
to go after her Internet trolls.
But the social media sites
don't like disclosing user info.
So it's hard to find out who's behind it.
You know, I don't really care
if it's legal or not.
Just find someone
who can track anonymous accounts.
How would I do that though?
I imagine way more people
are in your circle--
You remember Woo-jin's birthday?
Someone took a video.
-[intriguing music playing]
-Sorry, what?
And that someone still has it too.
Wait.
Wait. Who has it?
Wait, why? And how? What was recorded?
Was there anything bad in particular?
Was there anything
that happened at that party
that you'd want recorded
and shared with everyone?
Do whatever it takes.
I need to expose this account.
[Ye-ji] Hey, how's this one?
-Yeah, looks good.
-[Ye-ji] Should I choose one more?
How long is this year's
Healing Forest retreat again?
[Ba-da] It's a day, right?
What was that guy's name?
Kang…
That kid who died?
Kang In-han?
He died the day of
Woo-jin's birthday party, didn't he?
Yeah, he did. You're right.
[crowd cheering, laughing]
[cheering, laughing continues]
[intriguing music continues]
[sighs]
This is Yoon He-ra. How have you been?
I need your help with something.
[rhythmic pop music playing]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[woman 1] Everybody, listen up.
We are about to begin
today's floating session.
Relax your body and slowly lay back.
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[woman 2] Take a deep breath in.
Inhale.
[bowl resonates]
Good shot!
[both laugh]
-[music fades]
-[grunts, laughs]
-[camera shutter clicks]
-I haven't seen that kid today.
-Have you guys?
-I saw him earlier.
What do you think, guys? Is this it?
Kang Ha's last night on earth?
Oh, tonight?
I assume Chan-min
and the scholarship students wanna live.
-So they've got something planned.
-It better be something good.
Let's make it interesting.
Hey, Tae-ho, wanna bet on it?
[chuckles] Bet what?
I'll bet a million won
on the scholarship kid.
I bet he's stubborn enough to survive.
Me too. A million won
he makes it to tomorrow.
Oh. My million won says
he doesn't last the night.
A deal is a deal. All right, guys?
Park Tae-ho? How do you bet?
I also bet a million he doesn't.
Okay! That's two million if you lose.
-[Ye-ji] Yeah? Make it five.
-[Yun-seok] Five?
I raise you five more. Now it's ten.
Just pretend you're on a normal trip
with a normal school. This is your room.
These are more tucked away,
better for the scholarship students.
[Ha] Okay.
Sign up at the information desk
for any sessions you want.
My advice.
Do yourself a favor,
and choose the least popular ones.
We'll see. Thanks, man.
This doesn't make us friends.
Don't talk to me in front of the others.
There's a reason they call me "Moss."
My existence is barely noticed.
-That's a shitty name to call someone.
-I'm not offended by it.
I've worked hard for a long time
to earn that nickname.
I'm not about to ruin it.
Not for anyone.
Well, thanks for the advice.
[soothing music playing]
[door closes]
I've started looking into your problem.
You know, whoever's behind this account,
if they were at the party with us,
that probably means it's someone we know.
You'd think our friends would know better
than to try pulling this shit on us.
What do they want?
I don't know.
They never actually said.
Maybe they're hoping to make a buck
by threatening to make it public.
But who at the party
would be so desperate or stupid enough
to try and blackmail us for money?
Send me those DMs when you get a chance.
I'll get someone on it.
I'll send the messages on my own.
[He-ra] You must be
in serious trouble, Jae-i.
You weren't the only one filmed doing
something you shouldn't have been doing.
[door opens]
[knocking at door]
Brunch, anyone?
[Woo-jin sighs]
I haven't even touched my food,
but my appetite's gone.
-Could it be the vibes?
-Yeah, and I think it's contagious.
Because I feel the same way.
[Woo-jin] It's been forever
since we all hung out.
Can't you get along for one day?
[sighs]
I'm gonna head out.
Stay. You said you wanted to be friends.
There's no reason to avoid me
if you meant it.
Don't you remember what you told me?
That you would do "whatever it takes"
to try and get us back together.
That's reason enough, don't you think?
Hey, Jae-i!
Wait. I'll walk you back!
[sighs]
So my plan.
You thought about it?
[sighs]
Forget about the plan, He-ra.
It'll never work.
Jae-i would see through
a fake relationship in a second.
-She'd know.
-With the right girl, she might not.
I'll do it.
You? Why? What makes you
so perfect for the job?
It has to be someone Jae-i would believe,
but also someone who's willing to back off
the moment she starts to get jealous.
Trust me. I'm your only option.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but even though
Jae-i still has feelings for you,
she's crushing on the scholarship kid.
I can clearly tell
just from the look in her eyes.
If you don't do something fast,
it'll be too late to ever win her back.
[sighs]
[Ms. Han] I thought I packed all the meds,
but I forgot to bring any antacids.
Three boxes should be plenty.
Kang Ha.
I chose you for this
to help you avoid the other students.
Well, thanks, I guess.
Call me cowardly if you want,
but that's how this place works.
All I can do
is try to make the best of the situation.
You don't need to explain it to me.
This place is just cowardly adults
afraid of insane children.
I'm not even curious why anymore.
[sighs]
-Whoa!
-[brakes squeal]
Hey.
Jesus! You startled me!
I nearly ran you over!
-Are you going somewhere?
-Uh-huh.
On an errand to the drugstore.
Go on. I need to get more cigarettes.
What?
What? You want me to pedal?
-[pensive music playing]
-[He-ra] Huh? Isn't that Jae-i?
Yep, that's her with the scholarship kid.
[Ha] Hold on.
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
[romantic music playing]
[sighs] Feels good.
Hmm? What's that? I didn't hear.
Ah. You like the beach? Wanna stop by?
It's fine. Just keep going.
Sure.
[romantic music continues]
[music fades]
You want this?
No, thanks. I'm fine.
[Ha sighs]
I don't think it'll let up anytime soon.
[dog whimpers]
-Aw.
-[dog barks]
[Jae-i chuckles]
You're so cute.
[gentle music playing]
Ah! [laughs]
You're pretty.
What?
You know, you're pretty when you laugh.
I've never even seen you smile before.
[dog whimpers]
[Jae-i clears throat]
[chuckles]
I don't understand it.
You're pretty, smart, popular,
and rich enough to have
whatever you want in your life.
You got everything.
But you never smile.
[inhales deeply]
That's just the way I was raised.
I was taught to conceal my emotions
around others.
"Laughter today becomes gossip tomorrow."
"And if anyone sees you cry,
it's only a matter of time
before they use it against you."
Wait. That's how they raised you?
Mm-hmm. From the age of three.
Wow. [chuckles]
The rich really aren't
like the rest of us, are they?
What about you?
Everyone's always bullying you
for being poor.
What do you have to smile about
all the time?
What?
Who says I'm poor?
[laughs] That's funny.
I never thought of myself
as being poor or unhappy.
At least I didn't…
[chuckles]
…until I came here.
[music fades]
The rain isn't stopping. Let's just go.
Hey, Jae-i, wait for me.
Oh, right. The bike.
Jae-i.
Hey, Jae-i.
One second.
Put this on. You'll catch a cold.
There you go.
[chuckles]
Jae-i.
[Chan-min groans]
Shit!
[Chan-min gasps]
[whimpers]
Remember, when you see him,
grab him by the arms.
We'll either beat him up
or light a fire in here
and lock him inside.
We're gonna teach him
a lesson he'll never forget.
Understand?
Answer me.
I'll see ya.
Wait.
Dry your shirt. I have a closet steamer.
[woman 1] This place is really amazing.
I heard the suites here
can cost a few million won a night.
I wish they put me up in one.
[woman 2] That's nothing. Get this.
Ri-an and Jae-i's villas
were close to ten million won each.
Wow! Must be nice
to be born with a silver spoon.
[woman 2] If only they'd been born
with some manners to go along with it.
These kids order their teachers around
like we're housekeepers.
[woman 1 laughs]
I'm not sure
how much longer I'll last here.
You have it the worst!
Your class has Ri-an,
He-ra, Jae-i, Woo-jin too.
I don't think I would be able
to come to work!
[chuckles]
Those kids aren't too bad, actually.
It's some of the other students
who give me more trouble.
[woman 2] Hey.
Excuse me, Ms. Han?
The principal wants to see you.
Okay.
You'll have to excuse me.
-Go!
-Of course!
[woman 2] Hang on.
What would Principal Park
want with Ms. Han at this hour?
Who cares? Let's drink.
Okay.
[Ms. Han] Is something wrong?
My girlfriend isn't answering the phone.
Ah. Yeah, I left my cell phone behind
in my room to charge.
Wait. Did Principal Park
really ask to see me or not?
[chuckles]
I've got wine in my room. Let's go back.
[Ms. Han sighs]
[pensive music playing]
[music fades]
Where is Kang Ha?
What the hell's going on?
Does he know we're here?
Message the guys.
Get them to find out
what happened to this prick.
And where the fuck are the others?
There are supposed to be
four fucking guys here! I mean, Jesus!
[soothing music playing]
Take this. It's a change of clothes.
It's fine, really.
I'm not that wet anymore.
I'll leave as soon as my shirt's ready.
Well, suit yourself.
Do you know
if Kang Ha and Jae-i are close?
Who?
You know, Kang Ha the new student.
Ah, the scholarship kid.
Why are you asking?
DRYING
[man on TV] Good evening.
[woman] Has filming a gangster movie
rubbed off on you?
[man] You're not angry, are you?
[woman] No.
If you're tired, go sleep on the bed.
[Ha moans] No, no. I'm awake.
[man] Why don't we go somewhere
and have a chat?
[woman] Didn't you just come
from the film set? You must be tired.
I didn't hate it either,
you know?
[Ha] Hmm?
The night of the party,
when you kissed me.
Honestly, I didn't hate it either.
[romantic music playing]
[music fades]
Walking together? Where to?
Jae-i's villa.
I saw them going in together.
You did?
[Ri-an] Are you sure?
[Woo-jin] Yeah.
I saw them when I came back.
[breathes deeply]
-Just hang on--
-[disconnect tone beeps]
[rhythmic pop music playing]
I need to go out for a bit.
[Ms. Han] Okay.
[Ri-an] I know it's late, Principal Park.
But you need to come here now
with the master key.
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[In-han] I can help you.
[door opens]
[breathing heavily]
-[music fades]
-[Jae-i gasps]
What's going on here?
What do you think you're doing?
[pensive music playing]
PERSONAL INFORMATION FORM
KANG HA
[music fades]
[wistful music playing]
All of you,
you're worse than I thought.
Hmm? I didn't know ghosts could talk.
Why'd you even bother coming?
You're getting expelled today.
[Ba-da chuckles] I can't believe it.
A scholarship student
breaking into Jae-i's room?
I thought you were just a puppy dog,
but you're a total stalker.
[Ye-ji] Ugh, he's such a creep.
[Yun-seok] How much did we bet?
Five million?
-[Ye-ji] Don't remember.
-It was ten million!
-[student 1] Man, I'm hungry.
-[student 2] Wanna grab a burger?
Ri-an, where are you going?
You headed
to the disciplinary hearing as well?
Let's do it.
The thing.
What do you mean?
Your fake relationship idea.
Let's do it.
[sensual pop music playing]
I'm sure you're aware
why we asked you here, Mr. Kang Ha.
You've been accused of
entering Ms. Jung Jae-i's room
without permission
during a school retreat.
Do you deny this charge?
Answer the question!
There's no need for any questions.
I witnessed him there myself.
At least try to explain
how it happened, Kang Ha.
And if I did?
Would anyone believe a word I said?
[woman] This is Jooshin, Kang Ha.
We demand the utmost standard
of behavior from our students.
More than any other school in Korea.
And a student who refuses
to show any shred of remorse
cannot hope to be given a second chance.
[man 1] In accordance with Article 12
of the Jooshin High School regulations,
tainting the school's honor
and disorderly behavior,
we intend to expel Kang Ha
from his second year, class two.
He wasn't trespassing. I invited him in.
Jae-i.
He was just bringing over
something I asked for.
That's the only reason he was there.
If you really need to punish someone,
then punish me.
Come on.
Wait, you… [gasps]
[Ri-an] I don't believe this.
I came here
to personally ask the committee
to punish him for what he did to you.
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing?
[Jae-i sighs]
From now on, you leave Kang Ha alone.
[intriguing music playing]
What?
And before you ask,
I'm not using him.
I like him, all right?
[funky pop music playing]
You lay a hand on him, you answer to me.
[Ri-an] Stop.
This is Jooshin,
Jung Jae-i.
Don't start something you can't handle.
I don't care where we are.
I'm still Jung Jae-i, Kim Ri-an.
♪ Every time ♪
♪ Can't hold myself out ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ Won't make up my mind ♪
♪ But how many times do we just get by? ♪
♪ And so here we are ♪
♪ In this sanctuary right ♪
♪ Nobody else… ♪
Why'd you do that?
♪ Can make a sound ♪
♪ But I can hear it now ♪
[Ha] I could have dealt with it myself.
But because of what you just did for me,
people are going to turn on you.
Kang Ha.
Why did you really come to this school?
[unsettling music playing]
So I guess
you know who I am.
♪ Bow ♪
♪ Down before the their own god ♪
♪ Mind ♪
♪ The forces of your desire ♪
♪ Say ♪
♪ Where are we now? ♪
[singer vocalizing]
♪ Every time ♪
♪ Can't help myself but ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ Won't see any delight ♪
♪ But how many times do we just get by? ♪
♪ And so here we are ♪
♪ In this sanctuary right ♪
♪ Nobody else ♪
♪ Can make a sound ♪
♪ But I can hear it now ♪
♪ Down before the their own god ♪
♪ Mind ♪
♪ The forces of your desire ♪
♪ Say ♪
♪ Where are we now? ♪
♪ Down ♪
♪ Down before the their own god ♪
♪ Mind ♪
♪ The forces of your desire ♪
♪ Say ♪
♪ Where are we now? ♪
[singer vocalizing]
♪ Say ♪
♪ Where are we now? ♪
[music fades]
[melodic pop music playing]